<option option="Options introduction">
<p>Options for Bound-T are written on the Bound-T command
line before the name of the target program file.
An option begins with a hyphen, '-', followed by the name of
the option. This is possibly followed by a value for the option.
The option name and the value can be separated by an equal sign
'=' or by white-space (but not both).
</p>
<p>
Boolean-valued options, for example <option-ref option="verbose"/>,
can be written with a value, for example "-verbose=true", or without a
value, which implies a true value. Thus "-verbose" is the same as
"-verbose=true". If the option name is prefixed with "-no_" or "-no-"
this implies a false value. Thus "-no-verbose" is the same as
"-verbose=false".
</p>
<p>
There are also options with numerical (integer and floating-point)
values, string values, and keyword values (a fixed set of
option-specific strings, an enumerated type).
</p>
<p>
Some options that take a string value represent cumulative sets of
strings, for example sets of assertion-file names. Each occurrence
of such an option on the command line adds a new string to the set.
For example, each occurrence of the <option-ref option="assert"/>
option, with a string value, adds one assertion file (name) to the
set of assertion files for the analysis.
</p>
<p>
Similarly, some options that take a keyword value represent sets of
keywords (equivalently, sets of Boolean choices) and
each occurrence of the option can add or remove keywords from the set
while leaving other keywords in the set (equivalently, each occurrence
of the option sets or resets some of the Boolean choices while leaving
other choices unchanged).
Such keyword options accept a comma-separated list of keywords
or negated keywords (a negated keyword is a keyword prefixed with "no_"
or "no-").
For example, "-show bounds,no-loops" is equivalent to
"-show bounds -show no-loops" and neither affects the
setting of "-show spaces".
</p>
<p>
There are also some collections of related options that are named
with a common "prefix" followed by the actual name and value of the
option. These prefixes are
<option-ref option="draw"/>,
<option-ref option="imp"/>,
<option-ref option="trace"/>, and
<option-ref option="warn"/>.
Here, too, the prefix can be followed by a comma-separated list of
prefixed option names and values, without repeating the prefix.
For example, "-trace decode,calls" has the same effect as
"-trace decode -trace calls" and neither has any effect on the setting
of "-trace stack".
</p>
<p>The <option-ref option="help"/> option is a special command-line
keyword that makes Bound-T describe the meaning of other options.
It is used as follows:</p>
<p>
<nbsp/><nbsp/><nbsp/>boundt_&lt;target&gt; [options] -help [help arguments]
</p>
<p>
Here the arguments are:
</p>
<p><dl>
<dt>[options]</dt>
<dd>Options to select a target device, a cross-compiler, et cetera,
when there are device-specific or compiler-specific options.</dd>
<dt>[help arguments]</dt>
<dd>Zero, one, or two arguments to ask for help on specific options or
subjects.</dd>
</dl>
</p>
<p>
For more information on -help, run Bound-T with the arguments "-help help".
</p>
</option>
